https://www.anycount.com/privacy-policy/

T
?
T
!
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of AnyCount
This page is used to inform AnyCount’s visitors regarding our policies about the collection, usage, and disclosure of the Personal Information of AnyCount’s users.
Advanced International Translations operates the anycount.com website, which provides the Services of a directory of professional translation agencies.When you use AnyCount’s Services, you agree with the collection and usage of information, as described in this Policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used to provide and improve AnyCount’s Services. We will not use or share your Personal Information with anyone except in cases mentioned in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible at anycount.com, unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy. Information Collection and UseWe may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes: Personal DataPersonally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, and telephone number, and demographic information, such as your age, gender, hometown, and interests, that you voluntarily give to us when you register with the anycount.com, or when you choose to participate in various activities related to the anycount.com, such as online chat and message boards and subscription to newsletters and promotional emails. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the anycount.com. Derivative DataInformation our servers automatically collect when you access the anycount.com, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the anycount.com. Financial DataFinancial information, such as data related to your payment method (e.g. valid credit card number, card brand, expiration date) that we may collect when you purchase, order, return, exchange, or request information about our services from the anycount.com. We store only very limited, if any, financial information that we collect. Otherwise, all financial information is stored by our payment processor Paypal, or Shareit, and you are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. Data From Contests, Giveaways, and Surveys Personal and other information you may provide when entering contests or giveaways and/or responding to surveys.Log DataWhenever you visit anycount.com, we collect information that your browser sends to us, known as Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, our Services pages that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics. CookiesCookies are files with a small amount of data that is commonly used as a unique anonymous identifier. These are sent to your browser from websites that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve AnyCount’s Services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and to know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some of AnyCount’s Services. Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate AnyCount’s Services;To provide AnyCount’s Services on our behalf;To perform AnyCount’s Services-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how AnyCount’s Services are used.These third parties have access to the Personal Information of AnyCount’s Services users, so that the third parties are able to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose. SecurityWe appreciate your trust in providing us with your Personal Information; thus, we strive to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. However, remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Links to Other SitesAnyCount’s Services may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that we do not operate these external sites. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. Children’s PrivacyAnyCount’s Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to take the necessary actions.Options regarding your information Account InformationYou may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by:Logging into your account settings and updating your accountContacting us using the contact information provided belowUpon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.Emails and CommunicationsIf you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the anycount.comLogging into your account settings and updating your preferencesContacting us using the contact information provided belowUsing the unsubscribe link in newsletters If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly. Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page. Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
SupportKnowledgebase
Troubleshooter
Online Help
Text Count Standards
Submit Question
ProductFormats
Word Count Test
Localization
Let's stay in touch!
Subscribe to our Anycount Newsletter to receive great news, tips and unique offers.
* required
Facebook-f
Twitter
Linkedin-in
© 2020 Advanced International Translations. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
